{
  "title":"EDUCATION / EMPLOYMENT",

  "questions" : [
      {
          "question": "What do you like about school?",
          "id": "2010",
          "type": "TextForm"
      },
      {
          "question": "What don't you like about school?",
          "id": "2020",
          "type": "TextForm"
      },
      {
          "question": "Do you think you need extra help with any subjects at school?",
          "id": "2030",
          "type": "YNifSo",
          "ifSo": {
              "val": "Yes",
              "question": "If so, which subject(s)?"
          }
      },  
      {
          "question": "How well do you get along with the teachers at school?",
          "id": "2040",
          "type": "Emoji"
      },
      {
          "question": "Do you feel the teachers are fair?",
          "id": "2050",
          "type": "Radio",
          "responses": [
            {
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "answer": "No"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Some"
            }
        ]
      },
      {
          "question": "Do you feel the adults at school care about you?",
          "id": "2060",
          "type": "Radio",
          "responses": [
            {
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "answer": "No"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Some"
            }
        ]
      },
      {
          "question": "Are there adults at school you feel you could talk to about something important or personal?",
          "id": "2070",
          "type": "Radio",
          "responses": [
            {
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "answer": "No"
            },
      {
          "question": "Do you ever skip classes?",
          "id": "2080",
          "type": "Radio",
          "responses": [
            {
                "answer": "Never"
            },
            {
                "answer": "Once"
            },
            {
              "answer": "Occasionally"
          },
          {
              "answer": "Lots"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
          "question": "How well do you get on with other students?",
          "id": "2090",
          "type": "Emoji", 
          "responses": [
              {
                  "answer": "Yes"
              },
              {
                  "answer": "No"
              }
            ,
      {
          "question": "Are you being bullied in any way?",
          "id": "2100",
          "type": "YNifSo", 
          "ifSo": {
              "val": "Yes",
              "question": "If yes, in what way?"
          }
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you doing any work outside of school? (e.g: a job)",
        "id": "2150",
        "type": "YNifSo", 
        "ifSo": {
            "val": "Yes",
            "question": "If yes, then what work do you do?",
            "question": "How often"
        }
    },
    {
      "question": "Any idea of what you want to do when you have finished school?",
      "id": "2160",
      "type": "TextForm"
    }
  ]

      }

    ]

  }
  
